[{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980768366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":14713,"timeElapsed":88386},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980798801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":30432,"timeElapsed":118821},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980806331,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":7527,"timeElapsed":126351},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980811716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":5382,"timeElapsed":131736},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980821522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":9804,"timeElapsed":141542},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980825958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4434,"timeElapsed":145978},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980831678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":5718,"timeElapsed":151698},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980844575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":12895,"timeElapsed":164595},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980852849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":8272,"timeElapsed":172869},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980868810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":14142,"timeElapsed":188830},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980918223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":49411,"timeElapsed":238243},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980967700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":49474,"timeElapsed":287720},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980973757,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":6055,"timeElapsed":293777},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980984893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":11133,"timeElapsed":304913},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980989714,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":4819,"timeElapsed":309734},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980996096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":6380,"timeElapsed":316116},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981003139,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":7041,"timeElapsed":323159},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981006749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3608,"timeElapsed":326769},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981070393,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":61585,"timeElapsed":390413},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981074815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":4420,"timeElapsed":394835},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981079369,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":4552,"timeElapsed":399389},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981083939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4569,"timeElapsed":403959},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981094560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":10619,"timeElapsed":414580},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981099178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":4616,"timeElapsed":419198},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981103116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":3935,"timeElapsed":423136},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981109820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6701,"timeElapsed":429839},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981113392,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3570,"timeElapsed":433412},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981174011,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":59103,"timeElapsed":494030},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981180739,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6726,"timeElapsed":500759},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981188836,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":8095,"timeElapsed":508856},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981196816,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":7978,"timeElapsed":516836},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981203247,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":6430,"timeElapsed":523267},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981206800,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3551,"timeElapsed":526820},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981210423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3620,"timeElapsed":530443},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981213399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2974,"timeElapsed":533419},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981220615,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7213,"timeElapsed":540635},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981223641,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3025,"timeElapsed":543661},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981236440,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":11157,"timeElapsed":556459},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981240390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3948,"timeElapsed":560410},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981247739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":7347,"timeElapsed":567759},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981252462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":4720,"timeElapsed":572482},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981256811,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4347,"timeElapsed":576831},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981262787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":5973,"timeElapsed":582806},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981266328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3539,"timeElapsed":586348},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981282597,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":16267,"timeElapsed":602617},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981288890,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":6292,"timeElapsed":608910},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981297573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":7077,"timeElapsed":617593},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981302626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5050,"timeElapsed":622646},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981306665,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4037,"timeElapsed":626685},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981311004,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4337,"timeElapsed":631024},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981316264,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":5258,"timeElapsed":636284},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981320927,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4660,"timeElapsed":640947},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981323895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2966,"timeElapsed":643915},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981328739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4842,"timeElapsed":648759},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981333919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5178,"timeElapsed":653939},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981342468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":6263,"timeElapsed":662488},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981346118,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3648,"timeElapsed":666138},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981350015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3893,"timeElapsed":670034},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981354688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4671,"timeElapsed":674708},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981357542,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2852,"timeElapsed":677562},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981361267,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3722,"timeElapsed":681287},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981365650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":4380,"timeElapsed":685670},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981369137,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":3484,"timeElapsed":689157},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981376491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7352,"timeElapsed":696511},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981382259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5766,"timeElapsed":702279},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981395756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11935,"timeElapsed":715775},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981399491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3734,"timeElapsed":719511},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981403130,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3635,"timeElapsed":723150},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981406686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3554,"timeElapsed":726706},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981409925,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3237,"timeElapsed":729945},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981413099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3172,"timeElapsed":733119},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981417090,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3989,"timeElapsed":737109},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981420936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3844,"timeElapsed":740956},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981424357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3418,"timeElapsed":744377},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981433264,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":7286,"timeElapsed":753284},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981436577,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3311,"timeElapsed":756597},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981440542,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3963,"timeElapsed":760562},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981444567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":4022,"timeElapsed":764587},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981447740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3171,"timeElapsed":767760},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981451266,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3525,"timeElapsed":771286},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981454114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2846,"timeElapsed":774134},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981458036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3920,"timeElapsed":778056},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981463135,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":5097,"timeElapsed":783155},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981468784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4149,"timeElapsed":788804},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981472574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3787,"timeElapsed":792594},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981477301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4725,"timeElapsed":797321},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981480667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3364,"timeElapsed":800687},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981483777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3108,"timeElapsed":803797},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981486652,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2873,"timeElapsed":806672},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981490863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":4209,"timeElapsed":810883},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981494331,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3466,"timeElapsed":814350},{"subjectID":"k666u6srfh","prolificID":"672257bc1a2a2082750a1a44","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b256d10220bd71492c38","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981497464,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3131,"timeElapsed":817484}]